QINGSONG CEMENT FACTORY, WEIYANG CITY
REFORM FOR GROWTH
DRIVE SLOWLY, SAFETY FIRST
Sir. Busy? Have a drink.
No, thanks.
Anyway,
did the owner of the factory come today?
Which owner?
Mr. Song Qingsong.
I don't know about that,
but you can't park your car there.
If you're not here to get it fixed,
move it away.
Understood?
Get it fixed.
I'm here to get it fixed.
Look how damaged it is.
Check it and quote a price.
You parked at a great spot.
Your car is seriously damaged.
Did the other person run away?
Stop staring.
You won't see Song here.
Why is that?
Those who can see Song
won't come to me and ask about him.
But isn't it weird?
The place is locked up tight.
And the guard is strong.
One might even say
he's guarding an armory.
Have you not heard?
There was a gang fight here two days ago.
More than 200 men.
It was huge.
I lost some of my wrenches.
A gang fight? With whom?
Cripple Du.
Song's rival.
But why?
For business. The business in the mine.
The mine?
Dongshan Mine?
Do you see another mine in Weiyang?
It's run by the government.
Very lucrative.
QINGSONG CEMENT
PATTIA FRONT DESK
Uncle Ran,
now that we have checked
the underground labyrinth,
it's time to check the labyrinth upstairs.
We need to change our method for that.
Change our method?
We'll use Tremeaux's algorithm.
Tremor? Like land tremors?
Here.
Trémaux's algorithm
is the most time-intensive
yet the most likely to succeed
among all labyrinth solvers.
In short, take every route
and mark them so that we don't make
the same mistake.
In the end, we'll find the exit.
To translate it
into our investigation, it means
we have to first find a lead.
Uncle Ran, you make it sound
too complicated.
Forget about tremors. Just do this.
This is the entrance. This is the exit.
Now, you'll find the solution.
Give it back.
WEIYANG CITY DONGSHAN
MINE OPERATION CONTRACTOR TENDER DOCUMENT
Come in.
Mr. Song.
Hear me out.
Yesterday, I…
You did well last night.
You're smart.
This is your reward.
Mr. Song, I was just doing my job.
So, take it.
I…
Thank you.
When will you return the things
worth hundreds of thousands of yuan
stolen from Yuanlongli?
Immediately.
Where did you bury the woman?
After I was released yesterday,
the police have been following me.
I'll dig out the body now.
Did I tell you to do that?
Are you dumb?
Then, I won't dig the body out. I…
Burn it. Destroy it.
Dissolve it. Deal with it.
Okay.
Take a picture before you get rid of it.
AUTO MAINTENANCE, REPAIR SHOP
Mr. Song.
The officer from yesterday
is still waiting outside.
What if he follows me?
You made a mess and you expect me
to clean up after you?
If you fail to handle this properly
and the police find out,
you'll turn yourself in.
Otherwise,
I'll make your family disappear.
Let's see how long you can stay in there.
QINGSONG CEMENT FACTORY, WEIYANG CITY
I'M BRINGING XIAOHE TO YUANLONGLI. RAN
Yuanlongli?
Why that place of all places?
QINGSONG CEMENT FACTORY, WEIYANG CITY
Stop!
XINFENG AUTO REPAIR
Who told you to do this? You jerk!
Asshole!
Hey! Hey!
Song Qingsong, you son of…
Careful, Xiaohe.
Xiaohe.
Slow down.
Red, orange, yellow, green,
green, blue, purple.
Everyone is here.
Big butt!
-Big butt!
-What are you doing?
Let go!
Rat! Pickpocket! Money-grubber!
How come everywhere we go,
we always see you?
It's you again?
Mr. Qian. She is asking your question.
Officer Ran,
someone complained about a stench.
So, I came up here to check.
I thought someone
must have planted something.
Who knew that someone
was raising chickens here?
Unbelievable.
Why did you enter the chicken coop then?
To count the chickens.
How can I fine them without knowing
how many chickens are here?
I'll get someone from the management here.
This is unbelievable.
Unbelievable! I must clean it!
The chicken coop needs to be removed.
Qian!
-How dare you!
-Sir.
Sir.
What are you doing?
Qian Dajun.
Calm down.
Let me make myself clear today.
Touch my chickens
and I'll chop off your hands.
Sir. Calm down.
There's an officer here.
-Calm down.
-I don't care!
-Calm down. Calm down.
-Stay right there.
-Calm down.
Calm down.
-That jerk.
-Calm down.
Mister, you're amazing.
Did you raise all these colorful chickens?
Yes. Little girl, do you like them?
If you like them, I can give you one.
Thanks, mister.
Forget about it.
My mother won't let me raise it.
Give me a moment.
Thank you, mister.
I wonder what color this chick will be.
Hey!
It's a raw egg!
DANFENG MIDDLE SCHOOL
PRINCIPAL'S ROOM
Officer He, this is the place.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Come in.
Hello, Principal Qin. I am He Xiaohe.
I'm here for Han Zi'ang.
Oh.
Officer He. Take a seat.
Thank you.
Principal Qin, I know you're a busy man,
so I'll keep it brief.
I came to urge you
to reconsider the decision
to expel Han Zi'ang.
Officer He.
I already explained to you clearly
in our phone call yesterday.
It's a decision that we made
upon deliberate consideration.
But…
Please let me finish.
The expulsion isn't my decision.
In class, Han Zi'ang dozes off often.
And he often misses classes
for no reason at all.
This time, instead of truancy,
he stabbed someone outside.
Principal Qin, does Han Zi'ang
have a history of violence?
Not that I know of.
His homeroom teacher told us
that he was usually quiet.
But you know, the quiet one
turns out to be the most volatile.
This is just a stereotype.
From what I was told,
Han Zi'ang is indeed an introvert.
But that's because he likes to read.
Of course, what he reads are comic books.
Perhaps he mixed
fictional elements with reality.
When he heard that Yuanlongli was haunted,
he went on an adventure.
He ran into a homeless guy,
and then maybe, he was anxious and scared.
So, he stabbed him to defend himself.
Officer He, you're saying
that Han Zi'ang acted out of self-defense.
I get that.
But the parents don't get that.
He stabbed someone.
That's the truth.
If he comes to school,
the other parents will be worried sick.
He is still unconscious in the hospital.
The police are doing their best
to investigate the case.
Before the truth comes out,
I urge the school not to give up on him.
If someone lends him a hand
at a time like this,
you're not just saving his education,
you're saving his life.
Principal Qin.
In fact,
I was worse and more rebellious
than he was back then.
But someone in my life
never gave up on me.
He pulled me back in time
and saved my life.
That's why I can be
an officer like I am now.
Principal Qin, for a child,
one decision can determine his whole life.
I urge you to reconsider.
Perhaps you can be the one
who saves Han Zi'ang.
Officer He, how about this?
Since Han Zi'ang is still unconscious,
we'll delay his expulsion
as much as possible.
Before the investigation comes to an end,
I can speak on behalf of the school
that if the police
provide proof that Han Zi'ang
acted out of self-defense,
then we can reconsider the expulsion.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, Principal Qin.
Even at this age, Xiaohe is still a rebel.
She just swallows whatever hardships.
Sir, Xiaohe is almost like my junior.
She studied for six years
to be a criminal police officer.
Have faith in her.
She's my daughter.
Of course, I have faith in her.
I'm her dad, after all.
She also grew up under your nose.
But this is her first case.
She needs all the support she can have.
It was my first case back then too.
But you didn't pamper me.
Nonsense!
Did you acknowledge me
as your mentor back then?
The older you are,
the more grudges you hold.
NOTICE, YUANLONGLI INTERNATIONAL
GARDEN REDEVELOPMENT MEETING
THE MEETING WILL BE HELD AT 1 P.M. TODAY.
Why did they seal it off?
That side wasn't involved.
Why seal that place?
Let's go, sir.
SEALED, NANSHAN BRANCH
WEIYANG PUBLIC SECURITY BUREAU
I don't think we'll find anything here.
Should we go to the surveillance room?
Sir.
The surveillance room
was demolished a long time ago.
You already know about that.
Oh.
Then, let's head
to the underground car park.
I bet you have no idea
what it has become after all these years.
Sir, let's leave.
Just stay out of the case.
If this turns out to be a prank…
Eighteen years ago,
they also said the Xu Meng case
was a prank.
What did you do?
Sir, just tell the truth.
You want to keep me here in Weiyang
to investigate the case 18 years ago.
Qiao lives in Yuanlongli.
Don't you want to see her?
Officer Ran.
Qiao.
Sorry to disturb you again.
And this is…
Hi, miss. I am He Xiaohe.
My father is He Yuanhang.
He works with Uncle Ran.
Hi, Xiaohe. I am Qiao Suqing.
It's nice to meet you.
Miss, you're so pretty.
No wonder Uncle Ran
brought me here specifically.
Come. Come in.
Change your shoes.
Xiaohe.
What do you want to drink?
-This one.
-This one?
Then, Officer Ran…
Thank you.
-Here.
-Thank you.
Miss, your house is so clean.
And it smells good too.
Thank you, Xiaohe.
I'm living alone.
When I'm free, I like to clean my house.
You're living alone?
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
From what I know,
Uncle Ran doesn't have
a girlfriend either.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just telling facts.
Xiaohe.
Go take a shower here.
I'll come back later
to pick you up. All right?
No. I have to explore the maze with you.
You must stay here.
Look at you now.
When your father comes here,
how am I supposed to hand you back to him?
Come.
Xiaohe. Let's get you
all cleaned up, okay?
Officer Ran, don't let me keep you.
I'll take care of Xiaohe.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
Uncle Ran, you're blushing.
Am I?
Let's go to the shower.
Officer He.
What happened to you?
Is the case almost over?
I'm waiting for my tip-off reward.
So am I.
Please supervise the young one well.
Don't let him
get carried away by his needs.
Young one? Who?
Officer Ran.
I keep seeing him visiting Unit 415.
A mistress lives there.
Don't make things up.
I didn't.
I just saw him take a little girl
to the mistress's home.
Du, if you are bored,
study how the amazing detectives
solve the cases in your detective novels.
Don't just stare at your neighbors
and spread rumors.
But I…
You told me
to give you useful information,
didn't you?
I can't believe it.
Come. Eat while it's warm.
Wow!
Ms. Qiao.
You're just like a real-life super nanny.
You're a smooth-talker.
Dig in.
What's the matter?
It'd be great if I could call you
auntie in the future.
Witty, aren't you?
I've never thought
of Officer Ran that way.
You're lying.
I'm telling the truth.
I was just saying
I'd like to call you auntie.
Why did you think of Uncle Ran right away?
How dare you!
Coming.
You can't wait to see him.
You're…
Dad!
Xiaohe.
Officer He. Come in.
It's okay. I'm all dusty.
-I'm here to pick my kid up.
-It's okay.
Dad, I went inside
a chicken coop just now.
Did you go inside a pigsty or something?
I didn't get into a pigsty,
but I was harassed by pigs.
Officer He. Please come in.
Let me get you a fresh towel.
Sorry about that.
You even took a shower. Where's Uncle Ran?
He's solving the maze on the 18th floor.
Ms. Qiao's shampoo smells so good.
Her egg noodles are delicious too.
Dad, you must thank her
for taking good care of me.
Here, Officer He. Clean yourself.
Sure. Thank you.
My daughter must have troubled you a lot.
Not at all. She's so obedient.
Officer He, do stay here.
It's okay. I'll just wipe myself quickly.
Dad, I love Ms. Qiao.
Can Uncle Ran bring me here often?
Go. Wash the towel for Ms. Qiao.
Thank you.
Officer He,
I know I have a bad reputation
and that I should stay away
from Officer Ran.
But I am not what they say I am.
I only trust what I see with my own eyes.
Don't take those rumors to heart.
If you have done nothing wrong,
there's no need
to worry about false rumors.
COME TO THE OPPOSITE
OF THE FOOT MASSAGE PARLOR QUICKLY, LILI
Do you have to make a call?
You can use my line.
It's okay.
Can I trouble you
to look after Xiaohe for a while?
I might have to pick her up later.
Sure. No trouble at all.
I couldn't be happier that Xiaohe is here.
Me too.
Look at her.
Be a good girl.
Thank you so much.
FLEA MARKET
THE USUAL PLACE TONIGHT AT EIGHT
SEE YOU
What do you want?
Look at the car plate.
I am the deputy manager
at Qingsong Cement Factory.
Thugs like you best not touch me.
-I'm looking for you, you punk.
-For what?
A guy of mine, Wolfie,
was arrested by the police two days ago.
Do you know what happened?
No idea.
Do you know or not?
Yes. I know.
I know.
Your guy didn't kill anyone.
Don't tell me everything.
Just answer my question.
Okay.
Did Song Qingsong make the offer?
No.
I did.
I can swear on my life. I made the offer.
I'm trying to become clean, you know?
Since you made the offer,
pay up.
Pay what?
Your guy didn't even finish the job.
Why should I pay up?
Why? Why?
Did I tell you to do that?
Let's just be civil.
Be professional.
My guy is an important person
in the company.
And because of you, he was arrested
and is still not yet released.
Should we calculate the loss of profit?
The loss of profit?
Your guy didn't finish the job.
I had to clean up after him
and deal with those two.
You killed them?
Right.
I didn't know you were this ruthless.
One slash, one life.
Not bad.
What about my loss of profit?
That's easy.
We won't extort each other.
Aren't you the second in command
of the cement factory?
That's an important position.
Sign a contractor agreement with me
worth 300,000 yuan.
You're the client.
I'm the contractor.
Good enough?
Maybe we can just settle
the balance instead.
-Will you sign it or not?
-Yes!
Yes. Yes.
I like how decisive you are, Mr. Wu.
CONTRACTOR AGREEMENT
CLIENT: WU SHANLONG
CONTRACTOR: JIN MANSHAN
Tell them to tell Manlang.
Okay.
Speak.
Ms. Zhao forbids us
from mentioning Mengmeng.
My friends and I only gossip in secret.
They think a client is suspicious.
Who?
When he came, he only asked for Mengmeng.
And he paid double.
We call him Mr. Sun.
Mr. Sun?
He was already a regular at Pattia.
And he always came with a bag
of branded clothes.
The brands inside were so expensive.
Branded clothes.
Double Fish.
It's expensive.
Bowls.
This dress is probably
worth more than this unit.
Did Mr. Sun hand out goods
from Bowls and Double Fish?
Bowls and Double Fish…
I can't remember.
What is Mr. Sun's real name?
I'm not sure.
But after Mengmeng went missing,
Mr. Sun stopped showing up.
Sir, I've told you what I know.
I hope you can find Mengmeng soon.
I'm quite worried about her.
Don't worry. We've been searching for her.
Your information is very important.
Thank you, Lili.
If there's nothing else, I have to go now.
A HOME VISIT TO XU MENG’S UNCLE,
QIAO GUOQIANG.
CLEAR MARKS ON THE FLOOR
BY THE FOOT OF THE BED,
INDICATING IT HAS BEEN MOVED.
Oh.
When I was at Pattia,
a woman called Zhizhi
was quite close to Mr. Sun.
You can look for her.
Zhizhi.
Su Yuzhi.
A rich guy? What's his name?
Sun, I think.
His name?
I don't know.
She lied.
Adult Gaokao…
I thought only students sit for exams.
Adults have to do it too?
It's adult gaokao.
It's a chance for people like me
who never went to high school
to enter a university.
Oh. You want to impress Uncle Ran.
You're teasing me again.
Officer Ran is an ace student
from a prestigious school.
I started working after junior high.
So, I could only perform
physical labor,
like taking care of someone.
That's why I want to study hard,
get a degree, and find a good job.
-You can do this.
-Why do you say so?
Because you are the hardworking Ms. Qiao.
My mom told me that hard work
could make your dreams come true.
Your mom is right.
I, too, have to study hard.
-Do you even understand it?
-That's why I have to study.
I want to be an ace student
like Uncle Ran.
Then, let's have a pinky promise.
We will both
be ace students in the future.
Sure.
You make a pinky promise,
you keep it all your life.
YUZHI BOUTIQUE
The latest collection.
Pick anything you like.
Excuse me.
Cutie. You're finally here.
Are you here to treat me to hotpot?
No.
I'm here to ask you about Mr. Sun.
You said you weren't
close to him last time.
You lied.
Without lying, how else
could I make you come to me?
It's a game of flirting.
Su Yuzhi.
I brought him here.
So, tell us the truth now.
Cutie, what truth do you want to hear?
Please tell me who Mr. Sun is.
Sun's name is Sun Zhengyong.
He's from Fujian.
He has shares in my boutique, too.
Don't get the wrong idea.
We are not intimate.
What about him and Xu Meng?
If I tell you,
will you still come to me in the future?
Please… Please answer my question.
Did Sun Zhengyong give this dress to you?
Mind your tongue now.
I bought it from him. Wholesale.
FASHION BOUTIQUE
This is… A counterfeit?
Counterfeits sell like hot cakes.
So, Sun Zhengyong
bought the authentic products,
then made counterfeits
to sell them in wholesale.
Cutie, you're smart.
You figured it out.
How does he deal
with the authentic products?
Normally, he gives them to girls he likes.
He gives them to Xu Meng?
I guess so.
He likes Mengmeng the most.
Are you saying Mr. Sun has something to do
with Mengmeng's disappearance?
What do you think?
I don't know.
I saw them argue once.
When was it? And where?
At Pattia.
Mr. Sun was drunk.
He hugged Mengmeng
and asked her to be his girlfriend.
Mengmeng said no,
and Mr. Sun lost his patience.
He said Mengmeng played hard to get
and looked down on him.
They then argued.
-And then?
You raided Pattia.
Is there any place in Weiyang
that sells authentic Bowls dresses?
It's a huge brand.
There's one official store in Weiyang.
Right inside Weiyang Mall.
Can you give us the wholesale address
of Sun Zhengyong?
NANMEN WHOLESALE MARKET
NANSHAN DISTRICT, WEIYANG CITY
FASHION CLOTHING HALL
Oh.
Remember the surprise I promised you?
We have a rule. We can't…
I know.
I'll charge you the original price.
Five yuan.
Take it.
If you don't buy it,
she's going to lure you in again.
Thank you, Su Yuzhi.
I wish you a prosperous business.
See you.
Why not put it on now?
He.
I think Su Yuzhi
is telling the truth this time.
Of course.
She is so devoted to you.
He.
We're investigating a case. Be serious.
Sure.
Then, analyze this seriously.
Perhaps Sun Zhengyong
thought Xu Meng looked down on him.
His love turned into hatred,
and he killed her.
YONG'S FASHION
Let me meet him in his shop.
I'll visit the official Bowls store
to check when he purchased the dress.
Not bad.
You've learned how to narrow down
the scope from me.
That's progress.
Also, we shouldn't give up
on the lead on Song Qingsong.
Be patient. One at a time.
What happened to your head?
What could be so serious
that you couldn't say it on the phone?
What else could it be?
If it's about Song, forget it.
Forget it?
Wu Shanlong. Are you taking me for a fool?
Two plans.
And both times,
you told me they were foolproof.
Then, what happened?
You're putting it as if it were my fault.
You came to me first,
saying that we could work together
to scam money out of Song.
I don't care about his money anymore.
Can you even hear what you just said?
The police are after Mengmeng.
Song Qingsong wants me to turn myself in.
So, if you turn yourself in
and they interrogate you,
will you rat me out?
I knew it.
If men were reliable, pigs could fly.
I was forced to.
Do you have a plan or not?
Didn't you just say my plan was useless?
Zhao Hongmei,
let me remind you
that we're both in the same boat.
We're past the point of no return.
We can't do this forever.
Wu Shanlong.
I want you to tell me the truth.
Otherwise, forget everything.
Mengmeng.
Is she dead or alive?
She's dead.
Stone cold dead!
For goodness's sake.